Diego Diaz Medina

Fullstack Developer

DiegoDiaz(Link) DiegoDzm(Link) DiegoDzm(Link)

PERFIL

Full stack developer with studies in engineering, as a programmer I feel comfortable working in the front or

end, I learned more front-end technologies and I have experience in data analysis in SQL with Python. I have job experience in customer service and management

Proactive, responsible, pragmatic, oriented to work teamwork and achieve goals, enthusiastic about technology.

LANGUAGES

Spanish

Native

English

Conversational

EDUCATION

Full Stack Developer

4geeks Academy

12/2023 - 06/2024 | Santiago, Chile

Full-Stack course, React-js, Python, SQL-Alchemy, SQL (title in linkedin)

Informatics civil engineering

Universidad Diego Portales

01/2020 - 08/2023 | Santiago, Chile

3 years completed.(unfinished)

SKILLS

React Js

CSS

Python

HTML 5

SQL-Alchemy-Flask

MySQL

WordPress

Excel

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Programmer

Freelancer

06/2024 - Present

Technical support (Vtr)

05/2018 - 11/2020 | Santiago, Chile

Technical support by phone to VTR clients

Client service (movistar)

Atento chile

05/2013 - 06/2016 | Santiago, Chile

Client service by phone to movistar clients

PROJECTS

OnlineCV (Link) 2

Programming Portfolio